Piyush Bhor

Vulnerability Researcher - Waterloo, ON

piyush-bhor.github.io | linkedin.com/in/piyush-b-bb7394265 | piyushbhor22@gmail.com

SUMMARY

I am an experienced security researcher with over 4 years of software development and cybersecurity expertise. Currently, I work as a freelance vulnerability researcher for Trend Micro's Zero Day Initiative (ZDI) and occasionally as an AI trainer at Outlier. I hold a Bachelor's degree in Information Technology and am certified in ISC2 CC.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Security Researcher - Trend Micro Zero Day Initiative, Canada.

April 2023 - Present

- Performed vulnerability research by performing static and dynamic code analysis to discover zero-day vulnerabilities in the Linux Kernel, HuggingFace's Transformers, CatBoost, Behave, and Pip.
- Developed proof-of-concept exploits by using Python, C, and Bash to emphasize the impact of the zero-day vulnerabilities.

Al trainer - Outlier, US

January 2024 - Present

• Reviewed and rated code generated by AI models by assessing code correctness, adherence to instructions, presentation, and other criteria to improve model accuracy.

Web Developer - SuccessR, India

June 2021 - January 2022

 Supervised and led a team of 3 to develop and test React components by providing guidance and oversight to complete project requirements on time.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Advanced – Vulnerability assessment and exploitation, Exploit development (Python, C/C++ Bash), Reverse engineering of binaries and protocols, Penetration testing methodologies, Network security analysis (Wireshark, Metasploit, Burp Suite), Incident response and forensic analysis

Intermediate – Malware analysis techniques (static and dynamic), Threat intelligence gathering and analysis, Assembly language (x86, ARM), Creation and use of YARA rules, Implementation and management of SIEM tools (Snort/Suricata)

Basics – Linux system administration, Virtualization technologies (VMware, VirtualBox), Shell scripting, Containerization with Docker and orchestration with Kubernetes.

EDUCATION

Postgraduate Certificate, Computer Application Security	2024 - Present
Conestoga College, Waterloo, ON	
Postgraduate Certificate, Computer Application Development	2023 - 2024
Conestoga College, Waterloo, ON	
Bachelor of Science, Information Technology	2019 - 2022
Amity University, India	
CERTIFICATIONS	
ISC2 CC - Certified in Cybersecurity	2023
ISC2: Zero Trust Architecture in the Cloud	2023
ISC2: An Orientation to Cloud Native	2023
ISC2: Security Risk Management in a Small to Medium Business Environment	2023
REWARDS & RECOGNITION	
Seneca College - Seneca 2023 Smart Cities Hackathon,	2023
Conestoga College - IT Skills Competition 2023 (Web Design & Development)	2023
Amity University - Valedictorian, Bachelor's Degree in Information Technology	2022
Amity University - iPad 2020 - Innovative Project Application Development	2020

PERSONAL PROJECTS

- A Polymorphic RAT A polymorphic RAT (Remote Access Trojan) written in Python.
- Al Home Surveillance System Created using Python, the Twilio API, Raspberry Pi, and a custom-made circuit board for the IPAD 2020 competition.
- Portfolio Developed using Next.js, React, and TailwindCSS to create a personal website with a minimal and modern design.
- The Cannabis API Built with Node.js, Express, and MongoDB to create a REST API using a dataset from Kaggle.